pokerroom.com 2012-03-05

# 

Dated 30 November 2011 

As the operating company of the website www.PokerRoom.com, ElectraWorks Limited (hereinafter jointly referred to as "the Company") aims to actively work towards enhancing trust in data protection and thus takes every possible step to inform its users of all relevant security measures. 

Basically, you are able to move around our website freely without transmitting any information or data. Only when you wish to make use of our product line-up is registration and the transmission of data necessary. However, numerous safety installations prevent unauthorized third parties from accessing your personal data. 

In order to use our product line-up through the Company, you must first register yourself and therewith provide the following personal data: 

  * Gender
  * Surname and first name
  * Date of birth
  * Residential address
  * E-mail address
  * Confirmation that you are over 18 years of age (minors are not allowed to bet)

When you wish to deposit funds into your gaming account using a credit card, the following personal data is needed: 

  * Name and surname of cardholder
  * Name of credit card company
  * Credit card number
  * Expiry date of credit card

When you wish to deposit funds into your gaming account using a credit card, the following personal data is needed: 

  * Name and surname of account holder 
  * Name of bank 
  * IBAN 
  * SWIFT 

Before your first payout is allowed, you will be asked to send us a copy of an official document which includes a photograph of yourself (e.g. passport, identity document), either by fax or as an upload. You can be absolutely assured that only you receive your money. 

All personal data is stored in the database of the Company.   
For security reasons, your personal data will not be passed on to third parties, except for other companies of the bwin.party digital entertainment-group and Accenture Services Pvt Ltd, India, in any form whatsoever as a matter of principle, unless of course you give us permission to do so. Due to the license requirement of customer verification, the check of your personal data by an EU licensed and certified service provider is necessary. In the case of suspicious behavior personal data can be exchanged with your payment provider. So as to aid the prevention of fraud, match or price rigging, we are able to relay a suspected offender's saved details (information pertaining to the reservations or suspicions of the respective misdemeanor in question) to sporting bodies, authorities or any other third party, which deals with the investigation of such offences. For the purpose of research on the prevention of addiction, data can be made anonymous and passed on to the respective institutions. The Company naturally fulfils the valid legal regulations for the collection and processing of personal information. In the case you close your gaming account, your personal details saved in our system will, upon expiry of the legal warranty period and statutes of limitations, only be deleted at your express request. It is not possible to delete your details prior to this respite period, as this information must be available for your security should it be required for unenforceability, exertion or defense of legal claims by authorities or court of law. So as to avoid the nuisance of being troubled by third parties, we advise that you do not reveal your personal details in chat rooms or forums. 

### Prevention of Participation by Underage Persons

The Company reserves the right not to allow underage persons (under the age of 18) to take part in its product offers. For this reason the Company requests that potential customers confirm that they are of legal age and give their date of birth upon registration. 

In addition, the Company requests a copy of an official document, which includes a photograph, before every first payout. Should the Company, in the course of the above-mentioned verification, establish that a customer is underage; all transactions recoded in this account will be reversed regardless if gaming transactions were won or lost. The customer is barred from further play as of immediate effect. 

### Safety measures to protect personal data

The Company uses the latest security technology available to ensure you the best possible protection. 

To protect your personal data during communication with your web browser, the Company uses secure and tested encryption technology from VeriSign$reg;. Online transactions continue to be protected by the extremely reliable security system of a worldwide-accredited partner. 

### Further Technical Security Measures

In order to prevent illegal manipulation by third parties and to identify and prevent any form of misuse, we record the IP addresses of all computers used to access the line-up on the PokerRoom homepage. In addition, all your data is protected from unauthorized access by a firewall - a computer that is fitted with complex security technology specifically designed to shield the Company's network from the Internet. Additionally, the Company uses reliable internal data protection mechanisms combined with a restrictive security system. 

As a registered user, you have the option to change or revise your personal data (with exception of your first name, last name, date of birth and country) at any time. After logging in, you may correct your data under [My account / Settings: Personal details](https://www.pokerroom.com/account/profile/details/editPersonalDetails/#personal_details). 

As a registered user you may close your gaming account at any time. When your account is closed, any positive balance will be paid out to you and the personal data stored encrypted. Deleting personal data is not possible because in order to ensure your security, this information has to be available should it be needed in pursuing cases of fraud. With this exception, data is subsequently not used by the Company. The deletion of the personal data takes place with the expiration of the statutory period of limitation. 

If you have any questions regarding data protection, please contact our [Customer Service Team](http://www.pokerroom.com/help/contact/).
